<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Family Law | Attorney Directory</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/family-law/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 15:22:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.5.5</generator>
	<item>
		<title>A Comprehensive Guide to Your Family&#8217;s Legal Roadmap</title>
		<link>/a-comprehensive-guide-to-your-familys-legal-roadmap/</link>
					<comments>/a-comprehensive-guide-to-your-familys-legal-roadmap/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[roberto1122]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Nov 2023 05:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://localmarketingsuites.com/demo/attorney/general/?p=1086</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_0 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_0">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_0  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_0  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>Navigating the legal maze for your family can feel like exploring uncharted territory, but fear not! We&#8217;ve got your back in this comprehensive guide, helping you decipher the twists and turns of your family&#8217;s legal roadmap. So, buckle up, and let&#8217;s embark on this journey together!</p>
<p>When it comes to family matters, understanding the legal landscape is crucial. It&#8217;s not just about paperwork; it&#8217;s about creating a roadmap that aligns with your family&#8217;s unique needs and aspirations. Picture it like planning a cross-country road trip – you want to reach your destination smoothly, without unexpected detours or breakdowns.</p>
<p><strong>Getting Started: The Legal GPS</strong></p>
<p>First things first, you need a reliable Legal GPS. In the legal world, this is your initial consultation with an attorney. Think of it as the moment you plug your starting point into your navigation system. During this meeting, you&#8217;ll discuss your family&#8217;s dynamics, concerns, and goals. It&#8217;s the foundation of your legal journey, setting the course for what lies ahead.</p>
<p><strong>Mapping Out Family Law: A Highway of Options</strong></p>
<p>Now that you&#8217;ve set your course, let&#8217;s delve into the highway of family law. From divorce and child custody to spousal support and adoption, this highway has multiple lanes. Each lane represents a different aspect of family law, and your attorney acts as the skilled driver, guiding you through the traffic of legal complexities.</p>
<p><strong>The Intersection of Emotions and Legalities</strong></p>
<p>Family matters are not just about the law; they&#8217;re about emotions too. It&#8217;s like navigating through an intersection where legalities and emotions collide. An experienced attorney understands the delicate balance needed at this junction, ensuring that the legal decisions made align with the emotional well-being of your family.</p>
<p><strong>Packing Essentials: Documents and Evidence</strong></p>
<p>Just as you&#8217;d pack essentials for a road trip, you&#8217;ll need to gather your legal documents and evidence. This is like making sure you have your ID, insurance, and a map. Your attorney will help you identify what&#8217;s necessary, whether it&#8217;s financial records for divorce or documentation for an adoption.</p>
<p><strong>The Roadside Assistance: Legal Support Along the Way</strong></p>
<p>On any road trip, you&#8217;d want reliable roadside assistance. In the legal world, this is your attorney&#8217;s ongoing support. They are there to address questions, provide guidance, and ensure your legal journey stays on track. It&#8217;s the peace of mind knowing you&#8217;re not alone on the road.</p>
<p><strong>Handling Detours: Unexpected Legal Challenges</strong></p>
<p>No road trip is without detours. Similarly, your family&#8217;s legal roadmap may encounter unexpected challenges. These detours could be disputes, negotiations, or unforeseen legal hurdles. Your attorney, equipped with legal know-how, will help you navigate these challenges, ensuring you reach your destination despite the bumps in the road.</p>
<p><strong>Celebrating Milestones: Resolutions and Achievements</strong></p>
<p>As you travel down your family&#8217;s legal roadmap, there will be milestones. Maybe it&#8217;s a successful negotiation, a court resolution, or finalizing an adoption. Celebrate these achievements, for they mark the progress you&#8217;ve made on your journey.</p>
<p><strong>Arriving at Your Destination: Case Resolution</strong></p>
<p>Finally, the moment arrives when you reach your legal destination – case resolution. It&#8217;s like pulling into the driveway after a long journey. Your attorney will ensure that the resolution aligns with the goals you set at the beginning of your legal roadmap.</p>
<p>In conclusion, navigating your family&#8217;s legal roadmap is an adventure. With the right guidance, support, and a well-crafted plan, you can make the journey as smooth as possible. So, gear up, keep your eyes on the road, and trust that, with the right legal GPS, you&#8217;ll navigate the twists and turns with confidence. Safe travels on your family&#8217;s legal journey!</p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/a-comprehensive-guide-to-your-familys-legal-roadmap/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Protect Your Finances for Divorce</title>
		<link>/how-to-protect-your-finances-for-divorce/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-protect-your-finances-for-divorce/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[roberto1122]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:26:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://webagencyfortune.com/demo/v4/family-lawyer/?p=812</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_1 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_1">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_1  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_1  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner">If you think that you will be ending your marriage in the near future and you are uncertain what the future will hold for you, you may want to start taking the right precautions now. You have to make sure that you are protecting your financial security for later.

Reduce unnecessary expenses as soon as you can. Meet with your spouse and agree to cancel utilities and other bills. You will probably need to have money later on and this is a way to save money. Sell off your personal property that you do not need or want anymore. You can do this now to avoid losing it later on.

Cancel all of your jointly owned credit cards. You both should agree to cancel the cards and get separate ones. You need to cancel the cards because the spouse can charge up all kinds of different charge on the cards and you will get stuck paying them back. Canceling the cards now can save you money that you will need to have later on.

You may want to separate the jointly owned bank accounts. If you have bank accounts together, you may want to divide the money first. If not, your spouse may decide to go and take care of the money on their own and leave you with nothing. If you have outstanding bills for the home, explain this to the spouse so that the arrangements can be made to pay for them. If you do open up a different bank account, do it at another bank. Do not stay with the same company.

Stop contributing to combined accounts like 401K and pension plans. Telling your place of employment usually does this. Make the necessary arrangements so that your money is not being added to this account. You have to do this until you find out what will happen to those accounts and who will benefit from them.

Keep your job or try and find one. You have to make sure that you are protecting yourself and able to raise your family. If you are not getting any income from your spouse, you will have to do something to support your monthly needs. You may want to ask your ‘soon to be ex’ if they can help you financially until the divorce proceedings are over. This is only recommended if you are ending the divorce in a good way. If you are fighting over everything and not getting along, you need to contact your attorney and have them ask for you.</div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-protect-your-finances-for-divorce/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>When Child Custody Battle Go Too Far</title>
		<link>/when-child-custody-battle-go-too-far/</link>
					<comments>/when-child-custody-battle-go-too-far/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[roberto1122]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:24:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://webagencyfortune.com/demo/v4/family-lawyer/?p=807</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_2 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_2">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_2  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_2  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p><em>A story from one of our previous client.</em></p>
<p>A divorce is stressful enough, but when child custody is involved it can get ugly really quick. Unfortunately, there are times when the underlying reason for child custody isnt about the children at all. Its just one more way to get back at their Ex for all the “horrible things” that they have done. This is the worst situation because the only one who ends up getting hurt is the children. Thats why I felt compelled to write this article. My wife and I have been have been in a “heated” battle for her daughter for over a year now. Her ex-husband is a manipulative “know it all” who is purposely limiting my wifes contact with her daughter. My wife lost custody several years ago when she had to leave the state they were living in because of the constant harassment and threats being made by her Ex. At the time, the judge could not make a decision on custody and my wife was not allowed to take her daughter out of the state. It was not long after that her Exs high price attorney was able to get the judge to grant him full custody simply because my wife now lived out-of-state. Needless to say, my wife was devastated. She didnt think it could happen just like that with no consideration given to her situation. So in an instant, she went from having 50:50 custody to seeing her daughter only 6 weeks out of the year.</p>
<p>A couple of years later, I came into the picture and was able to convince my wife that she needs to stop being afraid of her Ex and it was time to fight for her right to be a mother to her daughter. That was easier said than done. By that time, her Ex had used his influence over his daughter to get her to blame my wife for everything that had happened. Soon the phone calls got shorter and shorter, and her daughter started saying awful things to my wife things that just tore her up inside. This 5-year girl was “yelling” at her mother for breaking up the family, for causing all her daddys “money problems”, and for leaving her behind to be with her new husband. None of which it true, but try explaining that to a 5-year old girl over the telephone with her Daddy sitting beside her and listening to the entire conversation. My wife was an utter mess, and even started blaming herself for what was going on.</p>
<p>We finally decided enough was enough, but we had no idea what to do next. I research everything. Im all over the internet look for tip and strategies, anything that can give us an idea on how to deal with a child custody issue. And wouldnt you know it; all I get are law firms that tell you that all you have to do is get the right lawyer. So that is what we did. We gathered all the money that we could, our entire savings and then some, and then hired a lawyer. A lawyer who called our situation an “atrocity”, and that he would do everything in his power to put a stop to it. And so it began, the child custody battle was in full swing. But after the first motion was sent out by our lawyer, we heard nothing. Days, weeks went by and no response, and when we tried to get in touch with our lawyer we had to set up an appointment where we would get charged $250 an hour to talk to him over the phone. A year goes by and nothing happens, except for the judge telling my wifes Ex to stop turning her daughter against her. And did I mention, we had a nice $16,000 lawyer bill.</p>
<p>This child custody battle was causing us all kinds of pain (emotionally, mentally, and monetarily), but we vowed not to quit. In the mean time, her daughter was angry at us once again because we were trying to “put her Daddy in jail” and “He would die of a broken heart if she was ever to go and live with mommy”. It was gut-wrenching to the both of us. And then something happened that gave us some hope. Did the lawyer call with some good new? No! Did the judge finally make a decision in our favor? No! I came upon a website talking about two experts (Doctors of Psychology) in dealing with child custody issues. With over 35 years of experience between them, and numerous expert testimonies, they looked they had something that they could teach us. And wouldnt you believe their guide on strategies in dealing with child custody only cost $89. I was skeptical at first, wondering what they could know that our lawyer doesnt. But what is $89 compared to $16,000, so I took a look. Right from the beginning, I noticed things that our lawyer never even mentioned to us. I even brought up some points from the book to our lawyer (at $250 an hour), and he acted like he had never heard of that before. These werent over the top legal tactics. These were simple things that none of us had ever though of. Were still in the midst of the custody battle, but things our leaning our way for the first time ever. All I can say is that the guide has helped me understand a lot more about child custody strategies, and I had only wished that I had found before all of this started. If you our in similar situation yourself, or about to fight for custody, I urge you to get this guide. Its a small price to pay in the long run, and it even shows you ways to make your lawyer work harder for you.</p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/when-child-custody-battle-go-too-far/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Protect Yourself From Divorce</title>
		<link>/how-to-protect-yourself-from-divorce/</link>
					<comments>/how-to-protect-yourself-from-divorce/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[roberto1122]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:19:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://webagencyfortune.com/demo/v4/family-lawyer/?p=803</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_3 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_3">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_3  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_3  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner">When you learn that you are going to be getting divorced, it may be have been coming for a long time or it may come as a complete surprise. Either way, there are certain things that you can do for yourself, your children, and your finances. This does not mean that you have to take all of your bank accounts and all that you have and wipe them out.

You have to take the responsible interests throughout the marriage so that you can protect yourself and all that you before and after if the marriage ever dissolves. There are ways that you can act reasonably while you are protecting your interests. These are only precautions that you will need to take care of if the divorce is not being ended amicably.

Depending on how well you and your spouse can get along at the time of the divorce, you may choose not to act on some of the suggestions that are given. You may decide that you and your spouse can work arrangements for everything without arguing. Whenever possible, try and make everything go as well and as easy as you can.

You should always get an attorney when you are heading towards divorce. They will make sure that you are taking the necessary precautions so that you can protect what you have and all the assets you have accumulated during the marriage.

Try and protect all of your own personal property that you have accumulated over the years. You need to move papers and documents so that you are the only one that knows where they are. If you must present them at a court hearing then you must do so. However, you need to make sure that you can keep all of your valuables safe so that you have a better chance at keeping them throughout the divorce.

Once of the best things that you can do before you decide to get married, is make sure that you know the person. Get to know them for a long period before you decide to take the big step into marriage. You have to be able trust so that you can feel good about marrying them. Have a long engagement so that you can see if the person changes any. If so, you may want to get out of the relationship before you decide to marry. This could be the best thing for both of you.</div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/how-to-protect-yourself-from-divorce/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Five Things You Should Know in a Divorce</title>
		<link>/five-things-you-should-know-in-a-divorce/</link>
					<comments>/five-things-you-should-know-in-a-divorce/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[roberto1122]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 20:34:01 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Family Law]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://webagencyfortune.com/demo/v4/family-lawyer/?p=736</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<div class="et_pb_section et_pb_section_4 et_section_regular" >
				
				
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_row et_pb_row_4">
				<div class="et_pb_column et_pb_column_4_4 et_pb_column_4  et_pb_css_mix_blend_mode_passthrough et-last-child">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_module et_pb_text et_pb_text_4  et_pb_text_align_left et_pb_bg_layout_light">
				
				
				
				
				<div class="et_pb_text_inner"><p>Though it is good to have a happy marriage, when you face a hard situation, you should have the courage to overcome it. Usually circumstances for divorce occur bit by bit and not suddenly. If you happen to unfortunately enter into the divorce market, you may have to consider the following things on divorce to overcome the process smoothly. Relying solely on friends and family alone for advice would not help you much.</p>
<p>1. In US, law on divorce differs from one state to another. For example divorce in California is different from divorce in Wisconsin. Though they differ mainly on division of assets, divorce can be filed only in the state where you live. You can not go to another State which offers more on division of assets.</p>
<p>2. Nowadays, an uncontested divorce, also called as no-fault divorce has become more popular and common amongst spouses opting for divorce. Under this divorce, they have to mutually agree and understand that divorce is the only option for both spouses, after arriving at a basic agreement on splitting up of jointly owned assets. The process becomes easiest when there is no involvement of children out of the wedlock. For no fault divorce, lawyers are only required either on a minimal basis or they are not required at all.</p>
<p>3. Some states insist on a test divorce, under which separation is required during a trial period before grant of divorce. During the period of separation, the couple opting for divorce should live apart without any interaction in between. Under the circumstances of separation, couple will get to know each other and will try to live without the partner. Many times, people suddenly discover that they do not any more require divorce during the period of separation, and get willing and prepared to make adjustments on past differences.</p>
<p>4. In an at-fault divorce, any one of the couple breaches marital contract and has committed abandonment, infidelity or cruelty to the other partner. There are different kinds of cruelty such as verbal or emotional cruelty or physical cruelty. Some of the States do not require an initial trial separation for at-fault divorce. When both spouses become guilty of committing breach of marital contract, the principle of comparison rectitude is employed. This method compares the guilty parties and determines which party is guiltier. It is very difficult to prove the degree of guiltiness through mere word of mouth which can drastically change the direction of case and decide upon division of assets and property.</p>
<p>5. If you are facing the divorce right now, you should know the specific divorce law relating to your State in which the case is filed, even if you are under a stressful situation. A proper homework will enable you to face the situation with great courage and you will come to know and understand what to expect out of the case.</p></div>
			</div>
			</div>
				
				
				
				
			</div>
				
				
			</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/five-things-you-should-know-in-a-divorce/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
